[{"answer": "It's me", "docId": "Horse-Whisperer_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Hi", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Where is she now", "docId": "Horse-Whisperer_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Surgery! For wha", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " my friend, no matter what I do, this horse will never be the same", "docId": "Horse-Whisperer_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "It isn't right to make him suffer..", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "No, I'm just not that hungry", "docId": "Horse-Whisperer_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I don't want to lie down. I've been lying down enough", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Fit? You want to check my teeth.  Good crowd today. I think you'll have some fun. You going to stay for dinner", "docId": "Horse-Whisperer_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " Kind of trouble I'm in the mood for", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Well, that'll happen", "docId": "Horse-Whisperer_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "What stuff is that", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What are you looking at, young man", "docId": "Horse-Whisperer_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Long enough", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Look, even if it was nearer, that's just not what I do. I give clinics. And I'm not even doing them for a while. I'm heading back to that place right now. I got a ranch to take care of..", "docId": "Horse-Whisperer_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " Ma'am, first class to that place is a waste of good money. Now, am I being too polite here or when I say NO in that place, does that mean YES in that place", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "She will if you think she should", "docId": "Horse-Whisperer_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " No, that's not what I said. I'm not a dictator. If you feel you should come, then come. Just do whatever you think is right", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " Whatever you want", "docId": "Horse-Whisperer_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Fine", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Oh. You didn't tell me", "docId": "Horse-Whisperer_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " You don't", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Would you like to see that", "docId": "Horse-Whisperer_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " I don't care", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yeah, I hear about that", "docId": "Horse-Whisperer_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Well, my friend, I'll tell ya", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What does she do", "docId": "Horse-Whisperer_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Mmm. An editor", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Did you ask him to come visit", "docId": "Horse-Whisperer_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Did he mention it", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Ha... if you've never lived in a city with museums, theater, music, restaurants, uh... god, a million things, then it's something I can't explain", "docId": "Horse-Whisperer_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " You lived in that place", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "If I can survive rush hour, I figure I can handle grizzlies..", "docId": "Horse-Whisperer_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I don't sleep all right anywhere. But the house is fine", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Would you let me ride your horse", "docId": "Horse-Whisperer_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Of course I have", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "my friend, I'm not good at this kind of talk", "docId": "Horse-Whisperer_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "He's a good man, my friend is. He's got a gift, come from heaven above, I swear. But he's still a man. And a woman can lead a man into the middle of a mountain lake", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "What were you doing over in that place", "docId": "Horse-Whisperer_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "That right", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "It's just one night. If I get uncomfortable, I'll go over to my friend", "docId": "Horse-Whisperer_-The.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Promise", "qsentId": 42}]